WOMAN: I've been meaning to ask you for some advice about restaurants.
WOMAN: I need to book somewhere to celebrate my sister's 30th birthday
and I liked the sound of that place you went to for your mum's 50th.
MAN: The Junction? Yeah, I'd definitely recommend that for a special occasion.
We had a great time there. Everyone really enjoyed it.
WOMAN: Where is it again? I can't remember.
MAN: It's on Greyson Street, only about a two minute walk from the station.
WOMAN: Oh, that's good.
I'd prefer not to have to drive anywhere
But I don't want to have to walk too far either.
MAN: Yes, the location's perfect but that's not necessarily why I'd recommend it.
MAN: The food's amazing. If you like fish it's probably the best restaurant in town for that.
MAN: It's always really fresh and there are lots of interesting dishes to choose from.
But all the food is good there.
WOMAN: Is it really expensive?
MAN: It's certainly not cheap but for a special occasion I think it's fine.
MAN: It's got a great atmosphere
and before dinner you can go up on the roof and have a drink.
MAN: It's really nice up there
but you need to book. It's very popular as the views are spectacular.
WOMAN: Sounds good. So that's definitely a possibility then
Is there anywhere else you can think of?
MAN: If you want somewhere a bit less formal then you could try Paloma.
WOMAN: Where's that? I haven't heard of it.
MAN: No, it's quite new.
It's only been open a few months but it's got a great reputation already.
It's in a really beautiful old building on Bow Street.
WOMAN: Oh, I think I know where you mean - right beside the cinema?
MAN: Yes, that's it. I've only been there a couple of times
but I was really impressed.
MAN: The chef used to work at Don Felipe's, apparently
I was really sorry when that closed down.
WOMAN: So is all the food they serve Spanish, then?
MAN: Yeah. You can get lots of small dishes to share
which always works really well if you're in a group.
WOMAN: Mmm. Worth thinking about.
MAN: Yeah. There's a lively atmosphere and the waiters are really friendly.
The only thing is that you need to pay a £50 deposit to book a table.
WOMAN: A lot of restaurants are doing that these days.
WOMAN: I should have a look at the menu to check there's a good choice of vegetarian dishes.
A couple of my friends have stopped eating meat.
MAN: Not sure. I'd say the selection of those would be quite limited.
MAN: I've just thought of another idea. Have you been to The Audley?
WOMAN: No, don't think I've heard of it. How's it spelt?
MAN: A-U-D-L-E-Y. You must have heard of it
there's been a lot about it in the press.
WOMAN: I don't tend to pay much attention to that kind of thing
So where is it exactly?
MAN: It's in that hotel near Baxter Bridge - on the top floor.
WOMAN: Oh, the views would be incredible from up there.
MAN: Yeah. I'd love to go. I can't think of the chef's name
but she was a judge on that TV cookery show recently
And she's written a couple of cookery books.
WOMAN: Oh, Angela Frayn.
MAN: That's the one. Anyway, it's had excellent reviews from all the newspapers.
WOMAN: That would be a memorable place for a celebration.
MAN: Definitely. Obviously it's worth going there just for the view
but the food is supposed to be really special.
WOMAN: She only likes cooking with local products, doesn't she?
MAN: Yes. Everything at the restaurant has to be sourced within a short distance
and absolutely nothing flown in from abroad.
WOMAN: I imagine it's really expensive though.
MAN: Well, you could go for the set lunch
That's quite reasonable for a top class restaurant: £30 a head.
In the evening I think it'd be more like £50.
WOMAN: At least that, I should think. But I'm sure everyone would enjoy it.
It's not the kind of place you leave feeling hungry
though, is it? With tiny portions?
MAN: No, the reviews I've read didn't mention that. I imagine they'd be average.
WOMAN: Well, that's all great, thanks...